（早乙女）
だから言っただろうが→
See what I said?
そもそも　ありゃ技なんて呼べる
代物じゃね～んだよ。
And besides, that's not even
something I'd call a "technique".
だいたい最初にベル坊のミルクを
飲んじまった時の事　覚えてるか？
Do you remember what happened when you
drank Baby Beel's milk... the first time?
（男鹿）そりゃ…もちろん。
Uh... Sure?
ん？
ん…。
覚えてないなら　そう言えよ！
If you don't remember, then say so!
（ベル坊）((ダーブー！))
((待ってろよ。
今　冷ましてっからな))
Wait, it's cooling off now.
（黒ベル坊）((バババブビ！))
((なんだ？お前も飲みて～のか))
What, you want some too?
((ダバ！))
((ミャ！))
((ダーブーマー！))
((ダーブー！))
((ギギギー！))
((ダーブダーブ))
((ウギギギー！))
((ケンカすんじゃねえよ！))
Don't fight, damn you!
((いいか　お前ら！仲良く
飲まね～なら→
Listen you two!
オレが飲んじまうからな！))
If you two won't get along,
then I'll drink it myself!
((ダブ！))
((バベボ))
((ダーブー！))
((ブウウー！))
((ダブブブ！))
((あ～もういい！))
Enough!
((オレが飲む！))
I'm drinkin' it!
まあ　そんな感じだったかな…。
It kind of went like that.
その後は気付いたら
あんたに止められてた。
The next thing I remember, you'd stopped me.
よくそんなもんを
本番で使ったな。
I can't believe you actually
used that in a real fight.
いや～珍しく　あんたが
ケガしてっからさ～。
Well, you were actually wounded for a change,
こいつはいけるな～っと。アハハ。
ダハハハ！
so I thought "Hey, this might work."
さわやかに笑ってる場合かよ！
This is no time for chuckling!
Komainu-sama is Watching You
（早乙女）
まあいい　とにかく　これから
お前がやるべき事は一つ。→
Whatever. From now on there's
only one thing to do.
そのスーパーミルクタイムを
完成させることだ。
You have to perfect that
Super Milk Time of yours.
ああ　分かってるよ。
今度はベヘモットも→
Yeah, I know.
Next time Behemoth is going to
be back with his entire army.
全軍　率いて攻めてくんだろ？→
戦いの度に意識が飛んでたんじゃ
話にならね～。それにだ…。→
We can't have you losing
consciousness each time you fight.
And besides...
東条に出馬。あいつらも悪魔との
戦いに備えて力を付けている。
Tojo and Izuma are preparing themselves
with the power to fight Demons.
《あいつらが？》
（早乙女）うかうかしてっと→
They are, too?
You dilly-dally, and
they're gonna pass you up.
お前…置いてかれるぞ？
ふ～…しかしブラックベル坊の
件といい→
But man, it's not just Black Baby Beel,
どいつもこいつも勝手に事を
進めやがって→
but everyone that's doing things
however they damn well please.
聞く耳　持たね～生徒ばかりで
泣けてくるぜ。
All you students don't listen
to a damn thing I say.
Makes a man wanna cry.
お？そういや　あれから
ブラックベル坊は　どうしたんだ？
Oh yeah, what happened to
Black Baby Beel after that?
消えたのか？
（早乙女）あ？そこに居んだろうが。
Did he disappear?
Huh? He's right there.
あ？
ニョ？
何…やってんの？
What is... he doing?
（早乙女）将棋。
そうじゃなくて！
Shogi.
That's not what I meant!
なんで　こいつがここに居んだよ！
Why is he here?
しょ～がね～だろ。山に
置いてくる訳にもいかね～し→
What else could I do?
I couldn't exactly leave him up on the
mountain, so I brought him with me.
連れて来たんだよ。
マジか！
Bored with it
For real?
心配すんな！オレの前じゃ
おとなしいもんだ。
No need to worry. He's
completely obedient to me.
そうは見えね～けど…。
Doesn't look that way to me.
ダーブダ！
Look, he's happy to see Baby Beel, too.
ほら。こいつもベル坊に
会えて喜んでるぞ。
ブルル！
ンダ？
ギーア！
そうは見えね～よ。やっぱ。
Doesn't look that way to me, either.
（寧々）葵姐さん。
（由加）おはようっす！
Madame Aoi!
Good morning!
（ゴン！）
（薫）葵姐さん！？
ど～したんすか？
Madame Aoi!
What's wrong?
（邦枝）ん～色々あって疲れただけ。
Just... A lot happened, and I'm tired.
((うぎゃああああ！))
うっ　むふっ　エへへ
ワハ　えへ　うふ…。
あ　葵姐さん？いったい何が。
M-Madame Aoi? What in the world...
（姫川）ふっ…まるでゲームの時の
お前みて～じゃね～か。
She looks like you did
when playing video games.
あたし！？
使えね～って意味だよ。
Me?
By that, I mean "useless".
あんだって～！？
（城山）確かに。
Say what?
It is true that you couldn't figure out
the controls and just ran in circles.
操作も分からず
グルグル回ってたしな。
お前もだろ！
（千秋）楽しそうに味方を殺したり。
You were no better!
Killing your allies with
a grin on your face...
（夏目）あはは！ほんと。見事な
チームキルだったよね～。
Yeah, it was a splendid team kill.
（寧々）くっ！あんたら～！
You guys!
（由加）結局～一番　活躍したのは
ウチっすかね～。
I guess in the end, I was the most helpful!
（神崎）いや　それだけは　ね～わ。
No, I wouldn't say that.
神崎先輩　ひどいっす～！
Kanzaki-senpai, that's mean!
（神崎）ま　次のゲームをやる時は→
Well, the next time we play, I'll
show you my triple heel-drop!
オレのトリプル踵落としを
見せてやるよ。
次は　ねえって。
え～…。
Except there won't be a next time.
ま～またマンションを壊されても
たまらないもんね～。
He can't exactly have his apartment
building be blown up again...
（邦枝）
《な　何これ？みんな知らない
うちに仲良くなってる？→
What's going on?
When did everyone get so friendly?
一緒にゲームやってたせい？》
Because they all played video games together?
ウチらは　やってないけど。
（涼子）言うな。
We didn't, though.
Don't complain. We should
be happy we even show up.
久しぶりに登場できただけでも
ありがたく思わないとな。
《私が修行してる間に
何があったの？》
What happened while I was training?
《ていうか　もしかして
私だけ置いてけぼり？》
And wait, am I the only
one being left out here?
んん！
（寧々）葵姐さん！
（邦枝）う～？
Madame Aoi!
明日の日曜　レッドテイルの
総会やるんっすよ！
Next Sunday, we're having a
Red Tails general meeting!
ついては姐さんのうちで　やらせてもらってもいいっすかね？
So, is it okay to have it at your place?
う…そりゃ今までは　うちで
やってたけど→
Well, we've done them at
my place up until now,
もうレッドテイルを引退した
身だし。
but I'm retired from the Red Tails, so...
（寧々）手近な所がなくて
困ってるんすよ！
But it has to be close or it's a real pain!
（一同）頼みます！
Please!
ま　まあ　いいわ。
ただし場所を貸すだけだからね。
Fine, okay. But I'm just lending
you the place, that's all.
（一同）あざ～っす！
Thank you!
フン…。
（由加）
葵姐さんをレッドテイルに！？
Get Madame Aoi to rejoin the Red Tails?
（寧々）
みんな今日の姐さんの姿を見たろ。
Didn't you all see how she was acting today?
ボロボロ…。
それに　ひどく情緒不安定で…。
Wiped out.
And she seemed quite emotionally unstable.
だからさ！
へ？
That's why!
だからこそ！あたし達みんなで
葵姐さんを支えてあげるんだ！
That's why we, the Red Tails,
are going to support her!
（由加）な～るほど！
話が見えてきたっす！
I see! I get you now!
分かったね？明日は総会に
かこつけて→
See? We're going to use a
general meeting as a front,
うやむやのうちに葵姐さんを
レッドテイルに引き戻すよ！
and while she's still out of it,
drag her back into the Red Tails!
（一同）お～！
…っす。
Yeah!
シェイク　おかわり～。
Another shake, please.
（コマちゃん）
≪フフフ…お疲れやな≫
Have a long day?
別に。それより勝手に出てこないで
って何度も言ってるでしょ！
Not really.
And I've told you not to come out
on your own how many times now?
あなたのことは秘密なんだから！
You are a secret!
（コマちゃん）
おお　こわ…分かってるがな。
Ooh, scary.
I know.
せやから　ちゃんと学校でも
黙ってたやろ。
That's why I made sure
to keep quiet at school.
それと…明日　私の友達が
ここに来るけど→
Now then, my friends are
coming here tomorrow.
ぜっったいに妙なこと
しないでよね！
Don't do anything fishy, got it?
ん…。
（ふすまの開く音）
（諫冬）あっおかえり　葵ちゃん。
Welcome home, Aoi-chan.
ごめんね　いさちゃん　せっかく
来てもらってるのに　ほっといて。
I'm sorry, Isa-chan.
I know you came all this way,
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
ううん　やっぱり心配だし。
No, I was worried, so...
大丈夫　なんとか使いこなせそう。
Don't worry, it looks like I can use him.
そう…すごいな　葵ちゃんは。
Really?
That's amazing, Aoi-chan.
本当に　あの子を
手なづけちゃうんだもの。
I never thought anyone could tame him.
何　言ってるの。
みんな　いさちゃんのお陰よ。
What are you saying? This is
all thanks to you, Isa-chan.
（諫冬）((この人は邦枝葵さんと
言います。→
Her name is Kunieda Aoi-san!
話を聞いて下さい。→
Please listen to what we have to say!
悪魔と戦う方法が
知りたくて来たんです))
She came here to learn how to fight Demons!
（鈴の音）
（コマちゃん）((知らん　そんなん
どうでもええ→
I dunno, and I don't care.
それより諫冬。わしの言いつけが
守れん言うなら→
And besides, Isafuyu, if you're not going
to obey my orders, you're not different.
お前も同じや。
金輪際　力は貸さんで))
I'll be damned if I ever lend you my power!
((ええ！))
((ちょっと待ちなさいよ))
Huh?
Hey, hold it!
((いさちゃんは
関係ないでしょ！))
What does Isa-chan have to do with this?
((私が勝手　言って
連れて来てもらったんだから))
I made her bring me here!
（鈴の音）
((ほう…わしの声が
聞こえるんか))
Oh? You can hear my voice?
((ほなら　いくつか質問するから
答えてみい))
Then why don't you try answering
a few of my questions?
《私を試そうってわけ？》
He's testing me?
((いいわよ))
I accept.
Well then... The first question!
（コマちゃん）((では…最初の質問や))
（風と鈴の音）
((スリーサイズは　なんぼや？))
What are your measurements?
((はあ！？))
((だから…スリーサイズやがな))
I asked you, what are your measurements?
（コマちゃん）((上から順にいくつや？
何なら当てたろか？→
You know: bust, waist, hips...
Maybe I could guess...
せやな～上から７０…))
((ちょっと！失礼ね！→
Let's see, 70 cm bust?
Hey, that's rude!
勝手に７０台って
決め付けないでしょ！))
Don't just go making me in the 70 cm range!
（鈴の音）
((いやいや　お嬢（じょう）ちゃん
どう見ても８０ないやろ))
Now now, Miss. There's no way you're
breaking 80, that's for sure.
Pride
((あっあるもん！き　着やせする
だけだもん！ホントだもん！))
Sure I am!
I just look smaller in this outfit! For real!
（鈴の音）
（コマちゃん）((安心せえ→
Don't worry.
わし　でっかいのも　こまいのも
どっちも大好きや))
I love 'em equally, big and small...
Pride
((って！これ何なの！？
いさちゃん！))
What the hell is this, Isa-chan?
((はい…この祠のヌシ様は
力を貸してくれる代わりに→
Yes...
The master of this shrine always asks kind of
sexual questions before he'll lend you his power.
毎回　ちょっとエッチな質問を
してくるんです))
((ただの
セクハラオヤジじゃない！))
What are you, just some old
man sexually harassing people?
（鈴の音）
((人聞き悪いな～。むしろ破格の
条件（じょうけん）やろ→
You're not a very nice person.
It's actually quite a unique condition.
何の代価もなしに神様の力を
貸してもらえるんやで))
You can receive the power of a god
without any payment in return!
((まあ　ええわ　そない
答えとうないんやったら→
Fine then.
If you won't answer that,
then I'll ask something else.
質問　変えたろ))
((当然よ！))
Of course!
（鈴の音）
((今どんなパンツはいてんの？))
What kind of underwear are
you wearing right now?
((うっ！))
（ブチッ）
((あっ…))
((心月流抜刀術壱式…→
Shingetsu sword school, second style.
百華乱れ桜！))
Countless Petals Scattering Sakura Blossoms!
（爆発音）
（コマちゃん）((ぎゃあああ！))
((百華乱れ桜！))
Countless Petals Scattering Sakura Blossoms!
（邦枝）((百華乱れ桜～！！))
Countless Petals Scattering Sakura Blossoms!!
（コマちゃん）((ぎぃやあああ！))
((ハァハァ…))
((葵…ちゃん？))
Aoi...-chan?
((さっさと出て来なさい！
あんたみたいなのが→
Get the hell out here!
If you're what they call a god, then
I'll destroy gods and demons alike!
神様だってんなら
神も悪魔も私が滅ぼす！))
（コマちゃん）
((ちょちょちょちょい待ち！
わ　分かった！分かったから！))
W-W-Wait a sec!
I understand, I understand!
（コマちゃん）((わしの負けや。降参
やから　そないなもん→
I lose, okay!
See how I look? Just stop
swinging that thing around.
振り回さんといて～な。
お願い))
Please?
（コマちゃん）((グフ))
（邦枝）
((あんたが…この祠のヌシ？))
You're... the master of this shrine?
（コマちゃん）
((あっそんな…腐った生ゴミ
見るような目で見んといて～な))
Stop looking at me like I'm
some piece of rotten garbage!
((力があんのはホンマやで))
I got power, seriously!
（邦枝）
((じゃあ　協力してくれるのね？))
Then, you'll help me?
((そら　もう！ただ…))
((ただ？))
Well, it's just...
Just what?
((一応　儀式的なもんとして
なんや…ホレ→
For now, as like, a ceremony...
Like I was thinking you could, you
know, give some kind of offering...
お供え的なもんが
あればな～なんて思うて))
((お供え？))
((たとえば…))
An offering?
For example...
((たとえば？))
((今はいてるパンツ))
For example?
The panties you're wearing?
((く～ださ～いな～))
Please give them to me!
（爆発音）
((フン！))
…というような事が
あったにも関わらず→
Anyway, putting aside all that,
粘り強く仲を取り持ってくれて
曲（ま）がりなりにも→
it's all thanks to you that
I've turned that stubborn fool
into an ally and he listens to
what I have to say, more or less!
言う事　聞くようになったのは本当に　いさちゃんのお陰よ！
（諫冬）そんな…気にしないで。→
It's the least I could do.
Don't worry about it, I'm just
glad to be of help to you.
葵ちゃんの役に立てて
私も　うれしいから…。
（コマちゃん）フフフ…甘いわ→
Innocent fools.
このわしが黙って言う事を
聞いてるだけと思うなよ～。
You'd better not think I'll just
do what you say like a good boy.
ん～。
ダブン…。
ン～！
あ～分っかんねえ！
I dunno!
どうやったらスーパーミルク
タイムを完成させられんだ～？
How am I supposed to perfect Super Milk Time?
（カチャ）
（ヒルダ）何を寝そべっている？
What are you sprawling on the floor for?
ギャ！
おあ！
例の技　完成するんだろうな？
Perfecting that technique of yours?
先日のように　坊っちゃまがお前と入れ替わられても　大迷惑だ。
It was quite the pain when you switched
places with the master the other day.
フゥ…安心しろ
もう完成目前だぜ。
Don't worry!
I'm just about to perfect it.
な？ベル坊。
Right, Baby Beel?
アダ…。
フン…ならばよい。
Fine, then.
♪～　プリプリプリ…
ウソだって見透かしてやがる。
Damn it, she can totally tell I'm lying.
♪～　ドスコーイ…
ったくどうすりゃいいんだよ。
Man...
What should I do?
長いこと使ってるせいか　こいつもだいぶ　くたびれてんな～。
I guess using it so long really
did a number on this guy, too.
ダブー。
はぁ…とりあえず　新しいのを買いに行ってみっか。
Guess we should go buy a new one for now.
ダーブー！！
They should be here soon.
そろそろ来る頃ね。石矢魔高校が
あんな事になったせいで→
With Ishiyama High in its current state, we
haven't had a general meeting in a while, but...
しばらく総会も開いてなかったけどざっと３００人は集まるかな。
I suppose there should be
about 300 people coming.
（寧々）≪葵姐さん
おはようございます！≫
Madame Aoi, good morning!
あっ　来た来た　３００人。
Here they come, 300...
（邦枝）さん…びゃく？
300?
葵姐さん　お世話になります！
Madame Aoi, I'm always in your debt!
Uh, sure... Where are the other members?
いや　お世話はいいけど
他のメンバーは？
They're not here yet? Where?
まだ来てないの？どこ？
About that, Madame...
そ　それがですね
葵姐さん…。
まさか…。
Don't tell me...
Crap...
（寧々）《やばいっ！》（由加）《葵姐さんに…》
Madame Aoi...
...has noticed...
（涼子）《引き戻し作戦が》
（薫）《気付かれた！？》
...our plan to bring her back.
Don't tell me...
まさか～！？
（一同）うぅ～…。
...there's a whole lot more members
that have fallen into romance?!
（邦枝）色恋に　うつつを抜かしてる子が　増えてるんじゃ→
ないでしょうね？
（一同）へっ！？
Listen!
いい？レッドテイルは
代々　恋愛禁止よ！
It's traditional for all romance
to be forbidden in the Red Tails!
Forbidden, damn it!
禁止なんだってば～！
禁止なのよ～！！
Forbidden!
Madame Aoi... You're tearing up...
葵姐さん
涙出てますけど…。
You really aren't emotionally stable...
やっぱ　情緒不安定…。
Um, it's not romance or anything.
いや…その　色恋とかじゃなくてですね。→
葵姐さんが引退されてから
やっぱり　みんな…。
Since you retired, Madame Aoi, everyone...
うわぁ～！！
What the hell is that, Yuka?
（寧々）ちょ…何だよ由加！
S-Somebody just brushed
up against my butt!
い…今　腰のあたりを　誰かが
ススーッと触っていったっす！
D-Don't tell me...
《ま　まさか…》
（古市）で　優雅に家で
日曜を過ごしていた俺が→
And so you interrupted my lovely
plan to stay home this Sunday,
何で　いきなり呼び出されて
その上→
and called me out here all
of a sudden to do what?
You're telling me to drink milk?
「ミルクを飲め」とか
言われるわけ！？
Well, 'cause if I drink it
some serious crap happens.
いや～　俺が飲んだら
やばい事に　なっちまうからさ～。
I was thinking of using
a new milk bottle, so...
新しい哺乳瓶の使い勝手
どうかな～？と思って。
So? Why?
（古市）だから　ねえ
何で俺なの！？→
Why me?
Why do I have to drink milk in
the park at noon on a Sunday?
何で　日曜のまっ昼間に
公園でミルク飲まされんの！？
'Cause... you didn't seem busy.
だって　お前ヒマそうだし。
ヒィー…アヒャヒャ！また　それかよ！
That again, huh?
（アランドロン）≪古市殿～！→
Furuichi-dono!
Spin, spin, spin...
クルクル…ピタッ。古市殿の
果敢なるチャレンジに→
Furuichi-dono's bold challenge!
及ばずながら　このアランドロンもお手伝いさせて頂きますぞ。
Even if you didn't call me, I
shall come to your assistance!
お手伝いってなに！？
だから　何なのよ～！
H-Help me do what?
I'm asking you...
ハハハハ！
助かるぜ　おっさん！
Thanks a bunch, big dude.
Um...
≪あの～…≫
は？
ニャ？ニャバ。
Pardon me, but is there, perhaps,
a large shrine near here?
（鳥居）失礼ですが　このあたりに
大きな神社は→
ございませんでしょうか？
あ～。だったら　この先を
右に曲がって　すぐかな。
Sure. Just turn right and
go straight over that way.
（鳥居）ご親切に
ありがとうございます。
Thank you for your kindness.
Oh? Look at that, Shino.
（支倉）おや　見てごらんヨシノ
かわいい赤ちゃんだよ。
It is a cute baby.
Oh, it is!
（島津）わぁ　本当！
ダブー！
（鳥居）２人とも　行きますことよ。
Let us go, you two.
Yes, Madame.
（支倉）はい　お姉様。
（島津）それでは…。
If you will excuse us.
（アランドロン）≪古市殿～！≫
は？
Furuichi-dono!
（３人）あら？
Why do I have to wear this?!
だから～！何で　こんなカッコ
しなきゃなんないんだよ～！
Everything begins with the right outfit!
何事も　まず形からですぞ～！
さあ　私の膝まくらで→
Now, drink my hot milk while
laying down on my lap!
熱いミルクを…。
あ　あの～
その　これは…。
U-Um, this is...
Now then...
それでは…。
（支倉・島津）ごきげんよう。
Have a wonderful day.
あ　ああ…。キャーとか叫ばれる
方が　まだマシな仕打ち。→
Seriously, I would rather they
scream "Kya!" and run away.
あれが　本物のお嬢様と
いうやつなのか…。
Are those what you call
true high-society women?
ささ　古市殿！
ほれ　ほれっ！
Come now, Furuichi-dono!
Right. Tell me what you think
of the new milk bottle.
おう　早く新しい哺乳瓶の感想
聞かせてくれよ。
ダブダ　ダブダ！
お前らぁぁぁ～！！
You people!
（涼子）ふ　太ももに
怪しい感触が～！
I feel something strange on my thigh!
Something's breathing into my ear!
生ぬるい風が　耳元で！
ヒヒヒ…。
Akichi, what's the matter?
アキチー　どうしたんす？（千秋）触られた…。
I've been touched.
What the hell has been going on?
さっきから　一体なにが？
あっ！あひゃひゃ…。
Nene-san?
寧々さん！？
あひゃひゃ…。→
あひゃひゃ！くすぐったい！
こ…これは。
まさか　幽霊とか？
What the...
Could it be a ghost or something?
ここ　お寺じゃなくて
神社っすよ。
This is a Shinto shrine,
not a Buddhist temple!
ヒヒヒ…。
（邦枝）《やっぱり…》
I knew it.
ちょっと！何やってんの？
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
勝手に出るなって
言っといたでしょ！
I told you, don't come
out unless I tell you to!
M-Madame Aoi?
葵姐さん…。あ…何でもないのよ　何でも。
Oh, nothing...
《もう！私にしか見えないと
思って　やりたい放題して！》
Damn it, I'm the only one who can see him!
He's having a field day!
（鳥居）≪ごきげんよう≫
Greetings!
My, what a wonderful day it is.
ああ　今日は何て
素晴らしい日なのかしら。
We have finally found them, Madame.
ついに見つけましたね
お姉様。
Wait, aren't those...
あ　あれって確か…。
They're the Taniyurikai from St. Marian
Girls Academy, who took control of west Kanto.
（薫）西関東を制圧した
聖マリアン女学院の谷百合会。
うふふふ…。
（島津）ご名答ですわ。
You are correct.
We have looked for you for quite some
time, members of the Red Tails.
（鳥居）ずいぶん捜しましたわよ
レッドテイルの皆さん。
Finally, we have caught you.
（支倉）ここで会ったが百年目。
It is quite premature of you
to think too much of yourself
（島津）北関東を
制圧したからといって→
いい気になるのは
お早いですことよ。
after taking control of North Kanto.
（支倉）レッドテイルを倒し
関東統一を果たすのは…。
We will defeat the Red Tails, and unify
control over the entire Kanto region!
We...
この…谷百合会ですわ。
...the Taniyurikai!
キタ！
Here they come!
These guys...
こいつら…。
言いたい放題で
ございますですね～！
Doing whatever the hell
they want, the prissies!
Too bad for you, however.
それにしても残念ですわ。
レッドテイルの皆さんの→
We heard about a general
meeting of the Red Tails,
総会とお聞きして　こちらも人数を集めて参りましたのに…。
so we brought a considerable
number of members...
お見かけした所　たった６人。
But now that we're here,
there are only six of you.
While on our side, we have...
対して　こちらは…。
Greetings!
（谷百合会）ごきげんよう！
イヒヒ…。
（由加）マジ　ぱねえ数っす！
That's some crazy numbers they got!
This is bad...
《まずい。いくら何でも
この人数相手じゃ…》
No matter how strong they
are, against so many...
仕方ないわね。私も手伝うわ。
Sorry, I think I'm going
to have to help out here.
（寧々）ダメです　葵姐さん。（邦枝）寧々！？
You can't, Madame Aoi.
Nene?
We current members of the Red
Tails will handle this ourselves.
ここは　レッドテイル現役の
あたし達だけで→
始末をつけますから。
はぁ…。
マジ　びびるっす！
I'm seriously scared here.
（涼子）久々の出番で
こんな事に…。
We finally get some screen time,
and it turns out like this?
Hey, it'll be a good chance to shine!
まあ　見せ場があっていいじゃん。
Everyone...
みんな…。
My, my... That is quite saucy of you.
あらあら　ずい分
生意気ですこと。
マリア様も見てらっしゃる
ことですし→
Maria-sama is watching us, you know.
１０秒で片付けて
さしあげますわ。
We'll have you defeated in ten seconds.
Look, this is a Shinto shrine, damn it!
いや　だからここ神社っす！
それでは皆さん
よろしくって？
Now then everyone, if you please.
（谷百合会）はい　お姉様！
Yes, Madame!
Got it, everyone?
みんな　いいね？レッドテイルの
意地　見せてやるよ！
Show 'em just how stubborn the Red Tails are!
（レッドテイル）お～！
Yeah!
Now...
では…いったるでえ～！！
Get 'em!
Have a wonderful day!
（谷百合会）ごきげんよう！
ごきげんよう！
Have a wonderful day!
It's no use, Nene!
無理よ！寧々！
トゥッ！
あ…。
うっ！
うぅっ！
あ！
お姉様？
Madame...
あ…。
どうなさったんです？
What has happened?
（コマちゃん）すりすり～。キャハハ！おケツのあたりが
くすぐったいですわ～！
Something is tickling me near my butt!
まあ　おケツだなんて
はしたない。お姉様！
Butt? How vulgar, Madame!
うわぁ！
（コマちゃん）ヒヒヒ！
いや…なに？首筋のあたりに不気味な感触が～！
W-What?
I feel something quite eerie near my ankles!
（コマちゃん）フフー！
うわぁ～！ちょっと…
気持ち悪い！
H-Hey! This is very uncomfortable!
All my strength is being drained!
（鳥居）力が抜けますわ～！
え？
これって？
Is this...
さっきの？
心霊現象？
From before...
The poltergeist?
う…卑怯でございますわね→
That is not fair.
Red Tails, I do not know
what has happened here,
レッドテイルの皆様方。
何だか分かりませんが→
but you have used one
terrible weapon against us!
ひどく不気味な攻撃を！
M-Madame, I'm all tickly, I
can't get up any strength.
お姉様…くすぐったくて
力が入りません。
I cannot stand, either...
わ…私も
立てませんですわ。
で？１０秒で片付けるんだって？
So, clean things up in ten seconds, was it?
（鳥居）あ…うっ…。→
それでは　ごきげんよう！
Well then, have a wonderful day!
（支倉）お姉様　待ってぇ～！
（島津）マリア様～！
Madame, wait up!
Maria-sama!
Sheesh.
（寧々）やれやれ…。
（邦枝）よくやったわね　寧々。
You did well, Nene.
No. It was that poltergeist who let us win.
いえ…勝てたのは
例の心霊現象のおかげです。
自分らの力じゃ…。
It wasn't our doing...
Well, it turned out all right.
（邦枝）結果は　どうでもいいの。
ただ　土壇場でも決して→
But you didn't back down,
even when it looked hopeless.
諦めない　それが　総長にとっては
一番大事なことよ。
That's the most important
thing for being a leader.
もう　あんたは名実共に
レッドテイルの４代目総長よ！
You are now really, truly, the
4th Leader of the Red Tails!
姐さん…。
（邦枝）これでもう　総会だなんて→
Madame Aoi...
So you don't have to lie about there
being a general meeting any longer.
ウソつかなくて　いいわよね。
あ…。
Crap, you knew!
やっぱ　バレてたっすか？
Yup, figured it out a while back.
ええ。途中から。
フッ…フフフ！
（笑い）
Well, what a happy story!
（コマちゃん）いや～　めでたしめでたしやなぁ。感動的なもん→
Such a touching moment there.
見せてもろたわ。しかし
聖マリアン女学院いうんか→
But those St. Marian Girls Academy girls...
若さいうんは　それだけで
かけがえのない宝やなぁ…。
Such youth, such irreplaceable treasure...
Seriously...
（邦枝）あんた。
え？
You haven't repented one single
bit since the very beginning!
（邦枝）あの祠の時から
全然反省してない！
いや　ちょっと落ち着こう。
待って。待ってぇな！
Hey wait, just a...
Wait, wait I say!
（邦枝）百華乱れ桜！
Countless Petals Scattering Sakura Blossoms!
（コマちゃん）あ～　また乱れますか！
もう～！
I'm scattering off again!
Repent for you sins!
（邦枝）少しは反省しなさい！（コマちゃん）は～い！
'Kay!
フフフ…聖マリアン女学院も
よかったけど→
St. Marian Academy was pretty nice.
But those Red Tails girls weren't bad either.
レッドテイルの子らも　ええなぁ。
ぬいぐるみとか好きやろか？
I wonder if they like stuffed animals?
Then, I'll pretend to be
a stuffed animal, and...
せや　ワシ　ぬいぐるみの
フリして…わっ！
（コマちゃん）え　あの…今の　もしかして聞こえとりました？
Um... Did you just hear me?
ええ。全部ね。
Yes. I heard everything.
（コマちゃん）
アカン　また来る。あ～　ほらな～
何で聞こえたんやろ！？
How could you hear me?
So, what were Aoi-chan's measurements again?
Such up, you perverted dog!
Anyway, next time is a serious mystery!
St. Ishiyama Academy is
shut down in a snowstorm.
The delinquents, just like the legendary
counting song, are beat up one by one.
Who could be the culprit?
Everyone watching at home, try
and figure it out yourself!
On the next Beelzebub: And Then
There Were No Delinquents.
Next Beelze's Hint: Super Freeze Phenomenon!